serviceu.com 2004-06-05

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**   
It is the policy of ServiceU Corporation (hereinafter "ServiceU") to protect your personal privacy. Because your use of the ServiceU Site indicates your acceptance of the ServiceU Privacy Policy, please review this Privacy Policy carefully. ServiceU may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to the ServiceU Site. This Privacy Policy shall be applicable to any person or entity that directly or indirectly uses the Site or the Services ("Users").

Terms defined in the Terms of Use shall have the same meaning in this Privacy Policy.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  
**   
ServiceU is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We use collected information to provide or improve Services for Users, and as more particularly set forth below, we may use collected information to contact Users for a variety of reasons, including, without limitation, obtaining information from Users regarding their use of the Site and Services and ways we can improve them, and to send information to them regarding us, our Services, or our Partners, such as promotions and events. We use this information in ways we determine appropriate in our sole discretion, and we reserve the right to do so. We will not sell or rent personally identifiable information to anyone, and we will not disclose any collected information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

ServiceU collects personally identifiable information when you register for a ServiceU account, when you use certain ServiceU products or services, and when you visit ServiceU pages. ServiceU may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

When you register with ServiceU, we ask for personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name, email address, address, and zip code. Once you register with ServiceU and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. ServiceU also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, ServiceU cookie information, and the page you requested.

**Financial Transaction Information  
**   
We request information from a User on our Site if the User performs a financial transaction with ServiceU or a Customer of ServiceU. In this case, a User must provide information including but not limited to name, address, and financial information, including but not limited to credit card information or bank account information.

ServiceU may use a third party intermediary to perform the transaction processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and uses the information provided for the sole purpose of processing the transaction.

**Cookies  
**   
ServiceU employs the use of Cookies to collect information about Users and their use of the Site. "Cookies" are small computer files that ServiceU transfers to your computer that allow ServiceU to know how often you visit the Site and the activities you conduct while on the Site. Third parties, such as advertisers, may also use Cookies when you select their advertisements or links from the Site. However, we have no access to or control over these Cookies.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE  
**   
ServiceU will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. ServiceU may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

We have your consent to share the information;  
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of ServiceU to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary or appropriate in our discretion to assist us.);   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our Site violate the ServiceU Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific Services.

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Links  
**   
This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that ServiceU is not responsible for the privacy practice of such other sites. We encourage our Users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Site.

**ACCESSING AND CHANGING YOUR INFORMATION  
**   
You can view and update your personal information at any time by signing in to your account on our Site and changing your profile.

**OPT-OUT  
**   
We need to be able to communicate at times with all Users, and therefore we reserve the right to contact Users. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions in the e-mails or on the Site.

**SECURITY  
**   
Your registration or account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. The security of ServiceU account relies on your protection of your ServiceU password. Any disclosure of your password to a third party may result in access to your registration or account Information or execution of transactions. ServiceU uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions of financial and certain other information. Financial information is stored in encrypted form on computers that are not publicly accessible via the Internet. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
**   
ServiceU may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site.

**CONTACTING THE PRIVACY ADMINISTRATOR  
**   
If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you may contact [webmaster@ServiceU.com](mailto:webmaster@serviceU.com).
